<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Fourth Time Lucky</title>
    <link href="https://cavan.us/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://cavan.us" />
    <updated>2025-04-09T20:33:51-07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Peter Cavan</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://cavan.us</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Skagit County History</title>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Cavan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://cavan.us/skagit-county-history/"/>
        <id>https://cavan.us/skagit-county-history/</id>

        <updated>2025-04-09T20:30:00-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    A few local factoids. Primarily taken from "Natural Skagit - a journey from mountains to sea" by Tim Robbins and&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>A few local factoids. Primarily taken from "<em>Natural Skagit - a journey from mountains to sea</em>" by Tim Robbins and "<em>The North Cascades Highway</em>" by Jack McLeod. </p>
<p>Natural world, flora &amp; fauna</p>
<ul class="ul1">
<li class="li1">100 million years ago the coastline was along Idaho. Volcanic islands kept colliding with West coast, adding land. Mountain ranges rose up and gave us what is now Washington state.</li>
<li>The Juan de Fuca plate is being consumed under the North American plate. Magnitude 9 earthquake in 1700, will be repeated every 300-500 years. Moves 1-2” per year and will eventually be consumed back into the Earth.</li>
<li>Climate: coastal temperature rainforest. Less than 0.2% of land. Otherwise mostly Patagonia and New Zealand.</li>
<li class="li1">The Skagit River is 160 miles long and drains ten billion gallons of fresh water per day into Salish sea.</li>
<li class="li1">Skagit Gorge is almost 6000ft high. 1896 road commission said a route over it was not practical.</li>
<li>Salmon never ran in the Upper Skagit because of the Skagit Gorge.</li>
<li>Salmon provide food to 137 other species, including their own young and 58 bird species.</li>
<li>North Cascades feature the pika, a mouse-like animal with high internal temperature and thick fur. Has to live under 50F.</li>
<li>Tulips: Mary Brown Stewart imported bulbs in 1906</li>
</ul>
<p>Infrastructure</p>
<ul class="ul1">
<li>
<p class="p1">Dikes added from 1863 to give more arable land amongst the salty marshes.</p>
</li>
<li class="li1">Diablo Dam: 389 feet in 1930. Was tallest dam in the world.</li>
<li>Why is Diablo Lake teal? Rock flour - colloidal (suspended) particles of rock ground up by glaciers.</li>
<li>Northern State Park (Northern Hospital for the Insane) was designed by the Olmstead brothers, sons of the designer of Central Park</li>
<li class="li1">Ross Dam: finished in 1956. Was supposed to be another 125ft high - blocked by local opposition which also pretty much ended local dam construction.</li>
<li class="li1">In 1890s SR20 was expected to go more South. Rather than going to Ross Lake, head pretty well West from Twisp to Marblemount. Considered too steep and avalanche-prone.</li>
<li class="li1">SR20 remained open all winter in 1976/77 (drought).</li>
</ul>
<p>People</p>
<ul class="ul1">
<li>First permanent (European) Resident: Blanket Bill Jarman (and native Klallam wife) canoed from Port Townsend to Samish Island in 1852.</li>
<li>Puget Sound had 75,000 residents in 1890 and 1.1 million in 1910, driven largely by Alaska gold rush. </li>
<li>Concrete came out of a merger between Baker and Cement City in 1909. It now has half the population, given the closure of the cement plant in 1967.</li>
<li>Jack Kerouac manned the fire towers on Desolation Peak and Sourdough and Crater mountains.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Two Goals for Swansea</title>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Cavan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://cavan.us/two-goals-for-swansea-2/"/>
        <id>https://cavan.us/two-goals-for-swansea-2/</id>
            <category term="SAFC"/>

        <updated>2024-02-24T22:08:51-08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>By a half-hour into the Swansea game on February 24 we were 2-0 down. Let's take a closer look.</p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>By a half-hour into the Swansea game on February 24 we were 2-0 down. Let's take a closer look.</p>

<h2>First Goal: Ronald at 18 minutes.</h2>
<p class="p1"><strong>1. Initial Cross</strong>. We have three players on the crosser at different distances (bottom left of image - O’Nien, Seelt and Trai - so two of our ostensible CBs). Swansea have three receivers crashing into the box with two defenders on them. Dan Neil is technically involved (edge of the penalty arc) but barely moves a muscle until the goal. For all practical purposes it’s 3 on 2 if we can’t stop the cross, which we can’t.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--wide"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://cavan.us/media/posts/92/1-5.jpeg" alt="" width="2560" height="1433"></figure>
<p class="p1"><strong>2. Header</strong>. Cross bounces to middle of the three receivers who heads at Patto. All of O’Nien, Seelt, Trai and Neil can see the 3 on 2 situation but no one gets above a slow jog toward the action. You could argue they believe themselves too far away to impact the game; Hjelde, certainly not too far away, is a statue from here on.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--wide"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://cavan.us/media/posts/92/2.jpeg" alt="" width="2559" height="1437"></figure>
<p class="p1"><strong>3. Save</strong>. Patto palms away the header. The two closest attackers plus Styles are alive to the danger. Hjelde sees it but doesn’t move an inch; everyone else (who's closer than Ekwah) is walking.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--wide"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://cavan.us/media/posts/92/3.jpeg" alt="" width="2560" height="1434"></figure>
<p class="p1"><strong>4.</strong> <strong>Follow Up</strong>. Styles giving his all to stop it. Hjelde still in concrete. Patto had fallen almost upside down stopping the header and can only ineffectually flick out a foot from a prone position. 1-0 to Swansea.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--wide"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://cavan.us/media/posts/92/4.jpeg" alt="" width="2560" height="1438"></figure>
<h2>Second Goal: Ronald at 28 minutes.</h2>
<p class="p1"><strong>1. Our Intercept. </strong>Seelt cuts out a Swansea lob and lays it off to O’Nien. Their attackers, initially following the lob and then pressing, are all moving up at speed. We seem switched off - watching events while stationary or walking. The eventual scorer, Ronald, is at the top of the screen with Styles a couple yards away. Note that for later.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--wide"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://cavan.us/media/posts/92/1.jpeg" alt="" width="2560" height="1430"></figure>
<p class="p1"><strong>2. Under Pressure. </strong>O’Nien has attackers bearing down and feels he has to offload. Styles, Hjelde and Seelt are partially or fully blocked by pressers (and not making themselves more available) and he probably feels he doesn’t have time to turn toward Patto. Remaining options are to hoof it, keep the ball, or pass to Neil.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--wide"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://cavan.us/media/posts/92/3-3.jpeg" alt="" width="2560" height="1430"></figure>
<p class="p1"><strong>3. Fateful Pass.</strong> Swansea’s Paterson, who O’Nien can definitely see, is excellently positioned to intercept a pass to Neil. Allen, running forward from behind Neil, barges past and indeed intercepts. I can forgive the latter if I assume O’Nien couldn’t see Allen through Neil; the former seems poor decision making (in a rush and under pressure). </p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--wide"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://cavan.us/media/posts/92/2-3.jpeg" alt="" width="2560" height="1436"></figure>
<p class="p1"><strong>4. Start of Attack.</strong> At the moment of interception there’s danger but not unthinkably so - we have three defenders closer to the goal than Ronald and Neil is almost level. Unhelpfully, Styles has barely moved since phase one and so lost any hope of sticking with Ronald.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--wide"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://cavan.us/media/posts/92/4-2.jpeg" alt="" width="2557" height="1437"></figure>
<p class="p1"><strong>5. Dribble. </strong>Allen powers forward, surveying the situation as he goes. O’Nien is backpedalling between Allen and the goal, sensibly enough. Ronald is calling for it with both barrels. Hjelde is moving to a reasonable zone for a second defender but lacks the presence of mind to notice the massive danger behind him. Styles nowhere useful. </p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--wide"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://cavan.us/media/posts/92/5.jpeg" alt="" width="2560" height="1434"></figure>
<p class="p1"><strong>6. Cross. </strong>Allen crosses to Ronald. As it leaves Allen’s boot, the nearest red &amp; white shirt to Ronald is about ten yards distant. Styles still hopelessly behind and Hjelde hasn’t realized what’s lurking.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--wide"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://cavan.us/media/posts/92/6.jpeg" alt="" width="2556" height="1431"></figure>
<p class="p1"><strong>7. Shot.</strong> Ronald initially hits it into the turf and I think Patto expects more of a bounce. His initial body movement infers a higher shot then he can’t get his right leg fully out in time. 2-0 to Swansea.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--wide"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://cavan.us/media/posts/92/7.jpeg" alt="" width="2560" height="1433"></figure>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Moving from OneNote to Bear</title>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Cavan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://cavan.us/moving-from-onenote-to-bear/"/>
        <id>https://cavan.us/moving-from-onenote-to-bear/</id>

        <updated>2024-01-10T15:16:00-08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>I may do a post on why I moved to <a href="https://bear.app">Bear</a> later; for now, a brief comment on the transition.</p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I may do a post on why I moved to <a href="https://bear.app">Bear</a> later; for now, a brief comment on the transition.</p>

<p>If you've been a long term <a href="https://www.onenote.com">OneNote</a> user and want to jump over to Bear, you'll likely want to bring your old notes with you. That is possible, but can be a pain. </p>
<p>A brief search will offer all sorts of options: perhaps export as HTML, or Word docs (?), or copy manually (the horror), or <a href="https://github.com/epatters/onenote-export">online services</a> that pull from the Office API, or the Obsidian importer (then export back out to Bear), or a wide universe of Python scripts that scrape OneNote into a Pandoc conversion. </p>
<p>None of those worked well for me. The closest was <a href="https://help.obsidian.md/import/onenote">Obsidian's first-party OneNote importer</a> - it pulled in the first OneNote workbook I pointed it at, then steadfastly refused any further ones. If you go that route, I recommend having Obsidian pull all of your OneNote content at once, even if that complicates later organization.</p>
<p>What did work: find an old (v6.5) binary of Evernote<sup id="fnref:1"> <a href="#fn:1">1</a> </sup>. You won't find them on Evernote's site anymore but a brief search will bring up links. Install it and use Evernote's dedicated OneNote importer, then export that to Evernote's export format (ENEX). Have Bear import that ENEX and you're mostly done. </p>
<p>It's the least bad method I found by a large margin but there are quirks to be aware of.</p>
<ul>
<li>Bear uses a tag- rather than folder-based structure and will not respect the folder structure automatically. My work-around was to import one workbook at a time and apply folder-imitating tags (use the 'untagged' smart tag after each import). </li>
<li>The rich-text-to-Markdown conversion is... a mixed bag. All text content should be there; conversion of bulleted lists and tables is iffy. </li>
<li>Each note will have the creation date and time added (within the body) at the top, and "Created with OneNote" at the bottom. </li>
</ul>
<div class="footnotes">
<ol>
<li id="fn:1" class="footnote">
<p>Try <a href="https://cdn1.evernote.com/mac-smd/public/Evernote_RELEASE_6.5_453172.zip">this for Mac</a> and <a href="https://filehippo.com/download_evernote/6.5.4.4720.0/">this for Windows</a>. Working links as of January 22, 2024.<a href="#fnref:1" title="return to article"> ↩</a></p>
<p> </p>
</li>
</ol>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The (UK) Conservative Five Families</title>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Cavan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://cavan.us/the-uk-conservative-five-families/"/>
        <id>https://cavan.us/the-uk-conservative-five-families/</id>

        <updated>2023-12-15T14:59:00-08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    ERG: Brexit, brought down May. Common Sense: ERG but go hard on culture war. Conservative Growth: Truss. Libertarian, low taxes.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <ul>
<li>ERG: Brexit, brought down May.</li>
<li>Common Sense: ERG but go hard on culture war.</li>
<li>Conservative Growth: Truss. Libertarian, low taxes.</li>
<li>New Conservatives: socially conservative, moderate on spending (eg more for NHS). Spend more but only for Britons.</li>
<li>Northern Research Group: … what happened to leveling up?</li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How To Talk So Kids Will Listen, Adele Faber</title>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Cavan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://cavan.us/how-to-talk-so-kids-will-listen-adele-faber/"/>
        <id>https://cavan.us/how-to-talk-so-kids-will-listen-adele-faber/</id>
            <category term="booknotes"/>

        <updated>2023-09-10T15:00:00-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Handling their emotions Accept feelings Lists, drawings Fantasy No questions or buts Compliance Make it a game, voices Give choices&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <ul>
<li>Handling their emotions
<ul>
<li>Accept feelings</li>
<li>Lists, drawings</li>
<li>Fantasy</li>
<li>No questions or buts</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Compliance
<ul>
<li>Make it a game, voices </li>
<li>Give choices about how, not what</li>
<li>One word reminders of chores</li>
<li>Describe how I feel</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Dare to Lead, Brené Brown</title>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Cavan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://cavan.us/dare-to-lead-brene-brown/"/>
        <id>https://cavan.us/dare-to-lead-brene-brown/</id>
            <category term="booknotes"/>

        <updated>2023-08-20T14:51:00-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Public speaking: House lights at 50% Imagine audience are toddlers Studying leadership is way easier than leading A leader: anyone&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <ul>
<li>Public speaking:
<ul>
<li>House lights at 50%</li>
<li>Imagine audience are toddlers</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Studying leadership is way easier than leading</li>
<li>A leader: anyone who takes responsibility  for finding the potential in people and processes, and has the courage to develop that potential.</li>
<li>Things to change
<ul>
<li>We avoid tough conversations</li>
<li>We manage bad behavior rather than dealing with root emotions</li>
<li>Diminishing trust</li>
<li>Not taking smart risks</li>
<li>Defined by setbacks</li>
<li>Too much shame, not enough learning</li>
<li>Hiding opinions to avoid bad response</li>
<li>Rushing too quickly to solution</li>
<li>Values are gauzy</li>
<li>Fear keeping people from learning</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Courage
<ul>
<li>Rumble with vulnerability</li>
<li>Living into values</li>
<li>Braving trust</li>
<li>Learning to rise</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Get clear who to take feedback from. Ignore cruelty from the cheap seats so you don’t develop a very thick sin.
<ul>
<li>Choose people as a “square squad” to take feedback from</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Clear is kind</li>
<li>Deal with fears and feelings, or deal with so much more bad behavior</li>
<li>Daring to lead vs armored leadership
<ul>
<li>A knower vs a learner</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Cynicism and sarcasm are the worst
<ul>
<li>Assumption that sarcasm always (or often) attacking other</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Shame is the fear of disconnection, and has been considered the base emotion</li>
<li>Ready to give feedback when you can own part of it and connect it to their strengths</li>
<li>Emotions
<ul>
<li>First reaction is a shitty first draft</li>
<li>Share your SFD of situations with people</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>A brief foray into Linux (2023)</title>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Cavan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://cavan.us/a-brief-foray-into-linux/"/>
        <id>https://cavan.us/a-brief-foray-into-linux/</id>

        <updated>2023-01-23T14:44:00-08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>Every few years I get the bug to try out Linux - is this the year of the Linux desktop? My very brief notes from the 2023 version are below. </p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Every few years I get the bug to try out Linux - is this the year of the Linux desktop? My very brief notes from the 2023 version are below. </p>

<ul>
<li><a href="https://ghostbsd.org">GhostBSD:</a> buggy.</li>
<li><a href="https://www.freebsd.org">FreeBSD</a> full version: install directory too small.</li>
<li><a href="https://www.freebsd.org">FreeBSD</a> net install: fine, dull.</li>
<li><a href="https://www.debian.org">Debian</a> stable: probably fine, don't like Gnome 3.38. Old packages in general.</li>
<li><a href="https://www.debian.org">Debian</a> testing: fine. With various UIs:
<ul>
<li>Gnome 43: don't love.</li>
<li>Cinammon: ugly version.</li>
<li>KDE: ugly.</li>
<li>XFCE: fine, bit dull.</li>
<li>Mate: dull.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><a href="https://mxlinux.org">MX Linux</a>: no, too lite.</li>
<li><a href="https://manjaro.org">Manjaro</a>: fine.</li>
<li><a href="https://linuxmint.com">Mint</a>: good so far.</li>
</ul>
<p>Addendum (March 2023): Mint was my favorite of the distros tested, by a surprisingly large margin. There is no single reason why - it simply felt like the best combination of reliability, features and polish. I did not stick with it, for Linux rather than Mint reasons - returned to Windows then to Mac. </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Notes on Notes Apps (2023)</title>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Cavan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://cavan.us/notes-on-notes-apps-2023/"/>
        <id>https://cavan.us/notes-on-notes-apps-2023/</id>

        <updated>2023-01-23T14:39:00-08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>The output of my evaluation of notes apps: tested nine options, sticking with OneNote. A few comments in a thread.</p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The output of my evaluation of notes apps: tested nine options, sticking with OneNote. A few comments in a thread.</p>

<ol>
<li>Nothing, paid or free, ticked every box I wanted. Could not 'pay my way out' to the ideal option.</li>
<li>The import/export landscape for notes beyond text (rich text, attachments, etc) seems to have regressed. In ye olden days when <a href="https://evernote.com">Evernote</a> was a dominant player (and, to be fair, made a decent format in ENEX) the pathway was straightforward - get your notes to ENEX (perhaps with a temporary Evernote account), then your new service would likely import it. Various services have scaled back their import options, including Evernote (you can get around with an old .exe).</li>
<li><a href="https://www.notion.so">Notion</a> was perhaps the hardest to evaluate. It has a good web version, Windows and Mac apps (no Linux), few (relevant) caps on the free accounts, powerful templates, etc. You could run all sorts of businesses largely on Notion. But, it felt too heavy/busy for my needs.</li>
<li>If you're willing to stick to plain text or Markdown there are all sorts of options, from <a href="https://keep.google.com">Google Keep</a> to <a href="https://obsidian.md">Obsidian</a>/<a href="https://joplinapp.org">Joplin</a>/<a href="https://bear.app">Bear</a>/<a href="https://standardnotes.com">Standard</a>/etc. That didn't fit my needs.</li>
<li>The final four were OneNote, Evernote, Notion, Apple Notes. Notion addressed above. Apple Notes, being Apple + data, had quirks, such as importing everything with a December 2010 date. Evernote was a strong contender but feels in flux (in process of being acquired). OneNote is currently one of the ugliest options (refresh expected in Q2) and isn't great with export, but ticks the rest of my boxes for $0.</li>
</ol>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Lying</title>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Cavan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://cavan.us/lying/"/>
        <id>https://cavan.us/lying/</id>

        <updated>2022-12-11T13:53:00-08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>With the renewed focus on such mistruths, it seems worthwhile to categorize the primary forms seen over the past few months in American discourse.</p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>With the renewed focus on such mistruths, it seems worthwhile to categorize the primary forms seen over the past few months in American discourse.</p>

<p><br>Take, for example, the recent case of the inauguration attendees. How many turned up (explanation of debate)<br><br>I’d categorize the justifications to Sean Spicer &amp; Donald Trump’s comments into three buckets:<br><br>1. “Lying is bad, but they didn’t lie.”<br><br>There are already a substantial number of 9/11-Truther-style “there were actually over a million people at Trump’s inauguration but the MSM is lying to us!” theories. I won’t further elucidate how they might be mistaken.<br><br>2. “Lying is bad, but a lying Trump is better than a crooked Hillary.”<br><br>This realpolitik notion understands that Spicer &amp; Trump told bald-faced lies in recent days, and accepts that lying is a bad thing, but rationalizes their flaws as acceptable when compared to a greater evil (in their mind, Democrats in power).<br><br>3. “Trump lied, and that’s a good thing.”<br><br>This position is the hardest to parse, but a longer version is ‘we’ve had generations of scheming, elitist politicians who hate Real America . Donald might lie, but that just shows that he’s a real person who’ll always do what’s right for Real Americans.”<br><br>(why does this matter? they’ll lie about other things, and their supporters won’t care.)</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Seattle Fairmont &#x27;suite&#x27;</title>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Cavan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://cavan.us/seattle-fairmont-suite/"/>
        <id>https://cavan.us/seattle-fairmont-suite/</id>

        <updated>2022-11-20T14:50:00-08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>Took my wife to the <a href="https://www.fairmont.com/seattle/">Seattle Fairmont</a> to celebrate our anniversary. We upgraded to the "Suite Seattle Staycation" package, described as:</p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Took my wife to the <a href="https://www.fairmont.com/seattle/">Seattle Fairmont</a> to celebrate our anniversary. We upgraded to the "Suite Seattle Staycation" package, described as:</p>

<blockquote>
<p>A Suite Seattle Staycation: Enjoy an upgrade to a suite, guaranteed early check-in of 12PM and a late check-out of 4PM, complimentary self parking for one (1) vehicle and a $50 off massage and/or $50 off any facial during your stay at Penelope &amp; The Beauty Bar (reservations required) as compared to the fully flexible rate.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>We did not take advantage of the beauty bar discounts - they were silly expensive ($400-1300). It's a five star hotel, the spa is expensive, fair enough. </p>
<p>We were less impressed that we were suite-less. Our "<em>Suite Seattle Staycation</em>", to "<em>enjoy an upgrade to a suite</em>", got us into what seemed their smallest and most basic room. On mentioning this to the front desk - "<em>oh, yeah, that's not guaranteed. If we don't have a suite you don't get one</em>." Do you then get a refund for the upgrade? Ha, not a chance. </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
